原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     累
校对     累
时间轴     想念Gallifrey的Wholock    累
后期     累
总监     累
早上好  爷爷
Good morning, Grandpa.
怎么了
What?
听
Listen.
是头麋鹿
It's a cow elk.
它在干嘛
What's she doing?
它很聪明
She's a smart one.
我没看到它
I don't see her.
你看不到它的
You won't. You won't.
它把那只狼从孩子身边引开了
She's leading that wolf away from her baby.
它的孩子呢
Where's her baby?
躺在狼面前的灌木丛里
Laying in some sagebrush right in front of him.
当麋鹿还是幼崽时  它们没有任何气味
When elk are babies, they don't have any scent.
所以狼能找到幼崽的唯一办法
So the only way the wolf can find it
就是等它对妈妈失去信心  转而逃跑
is if it loses faith in its mama, makes a run for it.
我有点难受  孙子
I'm feeling a little sentimental, grandson.
我想看那只小麋鹿活下来
I'd like to see that little elk live.
我们帮它一把吧
What do you say we tip the scales in his favor?
跟在我后面  好吗
Stay right behind me, okay?
如果我们靠得太近  它就会跑向妈妈
We get too close, it'll make a run for its mama
那我们就帮倒忙了
and then we've screwed the whole deal.
我们怎么帮它
How are we gonna help it?
划出一小块领地  孙子
We're gonna mark a little territory, grandson.
来吧
Get to it.
就在一个地方吗
Just in the one spot?
随你  尽情地尿
Everywhere you can. Let her rip.
别尿我身上
Don't mark me.
泰特醒了吗
Is Tate up?
嗯
Yeah.
他在干嘛
What's he doing?
灌溉  他没事
Irrigating. He's fine.
回来
Get back in here.
嗯  这样
Yeah, well, that...
应该暂时能帮到它
that should fix him for a while.
我们现在干嘛呢
What should we do now?
我觉得
Well, I guess...
我们去看看牛吧
Guess we should check on the cattle.
牛看起来挺好
Cattle look good.
检查完了吗
We done checking on the cattle?
是的
Yep.
现在干嘛
What now?
现在我们可以做任何你想做的事了
Now we can do whatever you want.
我不知道我想做什么
I don't know what I want.
我们散散步吧
Let's go on a walk.
好主意
That's a great idea.
我以为经营牧场挺难的呢
Thought ranching would be tougher.
这不算经营牧场  孙子
This isn't ranching, grandson.
这算是战利品
This is the spoils of it.
什么意思
What's that mean?
这就是我们经营农场的原因
It means this is the reason we do it.
经营农场
Ranching's a...
经营牧场可不好干  孙子
Ranching's a terrible business, grandson.
不好干  为什么
Terrible? How?
从何说起呢
Well, where do I start...
我们无法控制牛肉价格
We can't control the price of beef,
或者干草  拉牛去拍卖场的柴油价格
or hay, or the diesel it takes to take the cattle to auction,
或者喂牛的干草价格
or the hay out to the cattle.
联邦法规
There's, uh, federal regulations
州里的法规
and state regulations
县里的法规
and county regulations
市里的人还起诉我们
and these people in the city suing us,
抱怨我们没有好好饲养他们的食物
and complaining about the way we raise the food they eat.
还有什么
What else?
暴风雪和干旱
Then there's blizzards and droughts
一半的牛群想在河里自杀
and half the herd is trying to kill itself in the river
另一半在围栏上找漏洞
and the other half looking for a hole in the fence
这样就可以站在高速公路中间被车撞了
so he can go stand in the middle of the highway and get hit by a car.
或者走进森林
Or wander into the forest
被狼  灰熊
and get eaten by a wolf or a grizzly...
或者又大又臭的大脚野人吃掉
or a big, stinkin' Sasquatch--
大脚野人是什么
What the hell is a Sasquatch?
我也不知道
I don't know.
压根就没有大脚野人  对吧
There's no such thing as a Sasquatch, is there?
反正我没见过
Well, I've never seen one.
既然经营牧场这么难  我们为什么要经营呢
Well, if ranching's so hard, how come we do it?
这就是人生啊  泰特
Because it's one hell of a life, Tate.
这就是人生
One hell of a life.
黄石
第三季  第三集
一旦人生想得简单点  真的很有趣
You know, when you boil life down, it's funny
每个人的需求并不多  不是吗
just how little you need, isn't it?
可惜再过几代就不存在了
It's a shame that in a few more generations this won't exist.
一百年来大家都这么说  贝丝
People have been saying that for a hundred years, Beth.
他们以为铁丝网会毁了边界
I mean, they thought that barbed wire was gonna ruin the frontier,
但是现在呢
but there it is...
边界就在我们周围
The frontier is all around us.
那不是边界  里普
That's not the frontier, Rip.
随你怎么说  但事实就是如此
You can call it what you want. But that's what it is.
我去上班了
I gotta go to work.
再见
See you.
你比看起来聪明
You know, you're smarter than you look.
话不多  但你很聪明
Not saying much, but you are.
你和看起来一样聪明  这就说明很多事了
Well, you're as smart as you look and that's saying a heap.
-检察长来了  -谢谢
- The AG is here. - Thank you.
你好  请坐
Hello, have a seat.
是好事吧
This should be good.
取决于你的观点
Depends on your perspective.
我刚和总统的幕僚长通了电话
I just hung up with the President's Chief of Staff
他们要任命里德女士为副检察长
and they're appointing Miss Reid to Deputy Attorney General...
美国副检察长  她才30岁
Of the United States. She's 30.
我知道
I'm aware.
他们要在华盛顿重塑形象
They're rebranding in Washington.
所以要找年轻人
They're looking for youth.
他们得逞了
Well, they sure got it.
我要任命一个临时工来主持特别选举
I need to appoint an interim and host a special election.
我还有三周就可以退休打高尔夫了  女士
I'm three weeks from the golf course, lady.
-不行  -我还有什么选择
- No. - What are my options?
你能在我摆平之前别退休吗
Can you please just stay on until I figure this out?
让他进来
Send him in.
现在你可以帮我解决下一个难题了
Now you can help me navigate this next quandary.
佩里州长  幸会
Governor Perry, a pleasure.
彼此彼此  这是斯图尔特检察长
Likewise. This is Attorney General Stewart.
埃利斯·斯蒂尔
Ellis Steel.
你好  请坐
Hi. Have a seat.
从何说起
Okay, where to begin...
你看过我们的提案了吗
You've looked over our proposal?
看过了
I have. Yes.
机场提案吗
This the airport?
你们要求州政府投资什么
What investment are you requesting from the state?
我们想要那块地
We want the land.
你们保留所有权  我们获得30年的租约
You retain ownership, we operate on a 30-year lease.
每个航空公司承担
The airlines are assuming construction costs
各自航站楼的建造费用
on their respective terminals,
我们会建造基础设施
we'll build the infrastructure,
合同管理和运营归州政府管
contract management and operations back to the state
原因很明显
for obvious reasons.
我们的建造成本刚过十亿
Our build costs are just over a billion.
我们想要四亿的土地
Now, we're looking for 400 million in land
以及十年五亿的税收补贴
and a tax subsidy of 500 million over ten years.
跟我说说数据
Talk to me about numbers.
公园每年大约有四百万游客
The park has roughly 4 million visitors a year,
多数人从杰克逊霍尔那边走
the majority flying or driving through Jackson Hole.
怀俄明州的科迪市车流量最大
Now, Cody, Wyoming sees the most automobile traffic.
我们觉得滑雪度假村开业后
We feel once ski resorts are operational,
机场每年可以接待两百万游客
the airport could see 2 million guests a year.
林务局同意租借度假村的土地了吗
Has the forest service agreed to the lease for the resort?
是的
They have.
12000英亩将分三个阶段开发
12,000 acres will be developed in three phases.
第一个度假村将在18个月后开放
The first resort will be open in eighteen months
三个度假村加在一起大约有两千张床位
with roughly 2000 beds available through our three resorts.
附属建筑
Ancillary building:
公寓  不属于我们的酒店
condos, hotels not under our umbrella,
延迟18个月到两年吧
those things lag by another 18 months to two years.
我担心的是
Well, here's my concern:
我觉得杰克逊霍尔
uh, I don't really look at Jackson Hole
本身的发展并不靠谱
as a model for responsible development.
你有价值数百万的二套房
You have multimillion dollar second homes
为当地人的生活定价
that are pricing the locals from living there.
杰克逊有多个卧室社区来接收无家可归的人
Jackson has multiple bedroom communities to absorb the displaced.
天堂谷没有这个
Paradise Valley doesn't have that.
利文斯顿可以开始发展了
Livingston is ripe for growth.
我们的城市规划师认为这座城市
Our urban planners feel the town could absorb 40,000 people
未来十年可以吸收四万人  它需要
in the next decade, and it needs to:
数百万美元的二套房交房产税
multimillion dollar second homes paying property taxes
而且无需额外的服务项目
into the community without drawing on its services
正是这个山谷所需要的
is exactly what this valley needs.
这些开发项目
And we're talking about between 3 and 6 billion
每年的税收收入可以达到30到60亿
in annual tax revenue generated by these developments.
你选好机场的位置了吗
Have you chosen a location for the airport?
一开始  我们以为天堂谷
Initially, we thought the golf courses
运动俱乐部的高尔夫球场可以重新利用
at the Paradise Valley sporting club could be repurposed,
但联邦航空局觉得那里的山谷太窄了
but the FAA feels the valley there is too narrow.
联邦航空局选择了这里
The FAA chose this location.
这片区域
This area here.
那是黄石
That's the Yellowstone.
那是传了七代的农场
That's a seven-generation ranch.
他不会卖的
He'll never sell.
那你就行使土地征用权
Then you'll invoke eminent domain.
试过了
It's been attempted.
他赢了
He beat it.
三百套公寓大楼
For a three-hundred unit condo complex.
这叫土地掠夺
That was a land grab.
七代农场主是否为经济发展
Did seven generations of ranchers infuse
注入了60亿
6 billion dollars into the economy?
这是发展  州长
That's progress, Governor.
发展是有代价的
And progress has a price.
凯特  可以取消我的午餐吗
Kate, will you cancel my lunch?
没问题
Absolutely.
我就知道你这笔钱花得值
I knew you'd be money well spent.
有什么发现
What do you got?
他们在建机场
They're building an airport.
他们是这么说的
So they say.
你知道在哪吗
Do you know where?
运动俱乐部
The Sporting Club.
不是运动俱乐部了
Not the Sporting Club. Not anymore.
操
Fuck.
关掉
Turn that off.
他见律师时才能关掉
Can only turn it off when he meets his attorney.
我是他的律师
I am his attorney.
三分钟后关闭摄像头
Shut camera in three.
什么鬼  杰米
What the hell, Jamie?
我只是照他们说的做了
All I did is what they told me to do.
你让我做的事  现在
What you told me to do. And now--
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
你到了以后
Now, you need to tell me exactly what happened
到底发生了什么事
from the moment you arrived.
绕桶赛小女孩
Little barrel racer girl,
她被打得半死
she was all just beat to hell.
警员把两个老男孩
And the deputies, they took these two old boys
关在马厩里
and they put him in a horse stall.
马厩里
In a horse stall.
不是巡逻车吗
Not the squad vehicle?
马厩里
In a horse stall.
让我给他们传递一个信息
And told me to send a message with 'em.
所以我们把他们扔进了受害者的拖车
And so we threw 'em in the back of the victim's horse trailer.
我开车带他们转了转
And I just drove them around.
我刹车踩得挺猛
And I worked the brakes pretty hard.
可能太猛了
Too hard, I guess...
谁把他们装进拖车的
Who loaded them in the trailer?
警员
The deputies did.
他们有没有可能在你去之前就被打了
Is there a chance that they were assaulted prior to your arrival?
不  我没看到
No, I didn't see--
有可能吗
Is there a chance?
当然  有可能
Sure. Yeah, there's a chance.
好
Yeah. All right.
你把他们装进了拖车
You loaded them in the trailer
因为你的车装不下两个罪犯
because your vehicle cannot accommodate two perpetrators.
他们告诉你还有其他的马被偷了
They had indicated to you that there were other horses stolen.
所以你把他们装进了拖车
So you loaded them in the trailer
这样他们就能带你找到被偷的马
so they could lead you to the location of the stolen horses.
-你是说  -听着
- Are you telling me-- - Listen.
当你开到这个地点时
While driving to this location
有一辆车停在你前面
another vehicle pulled in front of you
所以你为了保护你们三个人
so you were compelled to make a defensive move
不得不采取防御性措施
for your safety and the safety of the two men in your custody.
避免了事故后
After avoiding the accident,
你查看了被告
you checked on the accused
发现他们已经伤重身亡
and you realized they had succumbed to the injuries
因为他们之前被警员关在游乐场的马厩里揍了一顿
sustained by the deputies in the horse stall at the fairgrounds.
你记得我跟你说过的事吗
Do you recall the events I am repeating to you?
事情就是这样
That's what happened.
就是这样
It was just like that.
印在你的脑子里
Burn it in your fucking brain.
我不是在船上就是在河里
I'm either on a boat or in a river
或许我只是不想和你说话  祝你生活愉快
or maybe I just don't want to talk to you... Have a blessed day.
生活愉快
A blessed day.
臭傻逼
Fucking douche.
我可真容易被暗杀
I'd be easy to assassinate.
别勾引我
Don't tempt me.
我没有非法入侵
I'm not trespassing.
这不是我们的土地
It's not our land.
你也不是第一次了
It's not the first time you've done that.
我20岁时就尝试过所有的事了
You know, I ran out of things to do for the first time when I was 20.
我都有画面感了
That paints quite a picture.
你回头可以用来打飞机
Yeah, feel free to beat off to it later.
我在说啥呢
But who am I kidding,
你只能对着镜子打飞机  对吧
you only do that in front of the mirror, right?
-光线必须合适  -猜到了
- Only if the light's right. - Yeah, I figured.
你他妈要把机场建在哪里
Where the fuck are you putting that airport?
我说过了  我不参与日常
I told you, I'm not involved in the day to day--
扯淡
Bullshit.
我每天都开过这条路  你从来没出现过
I drive this road every single day, you're never here.
现在律师们和州长坐在一起
And now you're here every day
决定没收哪些财产时
while attorneys sit with the governor
你却每天都来这里
to decide what properties to condemn.
贿赂州政府官员获取情报可是重罪
You know, paying state officials for information is a felony.
你没干过吗
You've never done it?
我在尽我所能地赚钱
I've done about all you can do to make money.
你也一样
So have you.
你毁了很多公司  家庭和工作
You have broken companies, ruined families, ended careers
现在你却站在那里
and now you stand there
瞪着一双大眼睛盯着我
looking at me with those big, mad eyes
仅仅是因为别人也这样对待你了
because someone's doing it to you.
我们要做的
And all we're going to do
是让他成为蒙大拿最富有的人之一
is make him one of the richest men in Montana.
悲剧啊
Oh, the tragedy.
这不是他想要的  他想要土地
It's not what he wants. He wants the land.
你知道永远不会失去土地的诀窍吗
You know the trick to never losing your land?
找块没人想要的土地  这是唯一的办法
Find land no one else wants. That's the only way.
我会阻止你的
I'm gonna stop you.
怎么阻止
How?
再移一条河吗  贝丝
You gonna move another river, Beth?
我们会移回去的
We'll just move it back.
我们都不想在法院待上一年
None of us want to spend a year in a courthouse
但我们会的
but we will.
我们承担得起
We can afford it.
你呢  贝丝
How about you, Beth?
你家人承担得起吗
Can your family afford it?
你能抵挡我们进军的军队吗
Can you afford to fight the army we'll march in there?
给我们一个提案
Make us a proposal.
不要亏待你的家人
Make it very fair to your family.
我们不想打仗
We'd prefer to avoid a fight.
但我们也不怕
But we aren't scared of one either.
县检察官兰迪·哈珀要见达顿委员
County Attorney Randy Harper to see Commissioner Dutton.
-他在等你  -嗯
- He's expecting you. - Yeah.
你挺有种啊  把我叫到你办公室
You got a lot of fucking balls summoning me into your office--
你他妈疯了吗
Are you out of your fucking mind?
我才被你搞疯了  我得出庭作证
Out of my mind is me testifying in court,
你打给我了一通电话
to the phone call you made to me
让我派一名探员去攻击在押人员
asking me to send an agent to assault detainees.
什么电话
What phone call?
我录下来了  你个混蛋
The one I recorded, you asshole.
你以为这是我的爱好吗
Think this is my fucking hobby?
我的探员被派去抓两名袭击者
An agent of my office was sent to retrieve two assailants
他们被带上车时  身上明显有你的手下
who had visible marks on them when loaded onto a vehicle
殴打的痕迹
by your deputies--
我的探员有权把那辆车作为证据
a vehicle my agent had every right to hold as evidence.
只要你的探员背了黑锅
If your agent takes the fall for this,
我们就安全了
we're all clear.
可不嘛
Yeah, sure.
只要他在监狱里度过余生
I guess all he has to do is spend the rest of his life in prison
他的妻子和两个孩子
while his wife and two kids
在贝尔格莱德流浪就可以了嘛
rot in some fucking single-wide in Belgrade.
你愿意说服他吗
You want to pitch him that idea
还是你闻到
or are you starting to smell the reek
和州检察官达成豁免协议的臭味了
of an immunity deal with state prosecutors?
我只是让你给他们一个教训
I just told you to teach them a lesson.
没错  兰迪
Yeah, you sure did, Randy.
你是这么说的
I mean, that's exactly what you said.
嫌犯是本地人吗
Are the perps local?
一个来自路易斯安那州
One's from Louisiana,
一个来自密苏里州
one's from Missouri.
最后的地址是北达科他州的一个石油营地
Last known address is a oil camp in North Dakota.
把他们标记为无名氏
Toe tag them as John Does,
就说他们是被你的人从排水沟的卡车里拖出来的
say your deputies pulled them from a truck
体内的酒精浓度是法定标准三倍
in a bar ditch with three times the legal limit of alcohol in their system.
那受害者呢
What about the victim?
她什么都看见了
She saw everything.
好快啊
That was quick.
治安官说还需要一段时间
Sheriff said they'd need it for a while.
没有卡车和拖车  她还怎么表演
How can she rodeo without a truck and trailer?
我就是这么说的
That's what I said.
但他们说需要
But they said they needed it for...
需要什么
For what?
好像有个警员对那些混蛋下手太狠了
Guess one of the deputies took it too far with those assholes.
不是警员
Not one of the deputies.
我说的话会让我的探员坐牢
What I'm telling you could put my agent in prison.
我也可能因此坐牢
It could put me in prison, too.
那你还是别说了吧
Maybe you shouldn't tell it.
我姐也曾被打得奄奄一息
My sister was beaten to within an inch of her life.
他们做的其他事  我不能说
Whatever else they did... I can't say.
她也不会说
She won't either.
但我可以说
But I can say this:
敢碰我家人的人
a man who puts a hand on a member of my family
就别想再碰其他东西了
never puts a hand on anything else.
她只是挨了打吗
Is a beating all she got?
我也不知道
I don't know.
她不肯说
She won't talk about it.
我有点想拿着猎枪站在法院外面
I got half a mind to stand outside the courthouse with a shotgun
等着那些混蛋被保释出来
and wait for those sons of bitches to get out on bail.
你不用这么做
You don't have to do that.
大家都这么说  但是
Everyone says that, but...
他们的女儿又没有被打的鼻青脸肿
everyone's daughter isn't beat to shit
谁知道还发生了什么事
and God knows what else.
所以不要教我该怎么做
So don't tell me what to fucking do.
她不是你女儿
It ain't your daughter.
我没有教你该怎么做
I'm not telling you what to do.
我是说你不用这么做
I'm saying you don't have to do that.
80年前我们可以把他们吊在树上
Eighty years ago we could've hung them from a tree.
但今天
But today...
我能做的只有这么多了
this is the best I can offer.
我可以保证
I can promise this:
他们不会被传讯了
they're never getting arraigned.
你应该竞选州长
You should run for governor.
还是先说今天的事吧
Let's just focus on today.
你这么做是为了我吗
You did that for me?
我这么做是为了
I did that for every father
不让爱女心切的父亲犯错
who would be sacrificing their family if they did it.
他们没了
So they're gone.
他们完蛋了
They're done.
我不认识你  先生
I don't know you, sir.
我这么做说明我很信任你
And I'm showing you a lot of trust.
希望你也可以展示一下你的诚意
I need you to show me the same.
我想澄清一下这意味着什么
I just want to be clear about what this means.
你说得很清楚了
You've been plenty clear.
这样你就变成从犯了
This makes you an accessory.
你女儿要明白这一点
Your daughter needs to understand that.
我女儿一个字都不肯说
My daughter won't say a word
我恨不得亲手杀了他们
and it makes me more than that.
别担心
Don't worry about this:
地一干  什么都没发生过
soon as the grounds dry, it never happened.
但你我之间
But between you and me--
你肯定会需要帮助
time'll come you'll need a favor
我已经等不及了
and I can't wait to give it.
我可能真的需要你的帮助
I might ask for it.
凯特  帮我接通约翰·达顿
Kate, get me John Dutton on the line, please.
好的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
直接转到语音信箱了
It went straight to voicemail.
-试试杰米  -好的  女士
- Try Jamie. - Yes, ma'am.
我把他接进来
I'm putting him through.
-杰米  -州长
- Jamie? - Governor.
有什么事吗
What can I do for you?
我想和你们爷俩坐下来谈谈
I need to sit down with you and your father.
好的
Oh, okay.
你能说一下我们要讨论的大致内容吗
Can you give me the broad strokes of what we'll be discussing?
抱歉  今天没有大致内容
Sorry, no broad strokes today.
我们什么时候能见面
When can we meet?
州长  我能明天再打给你吗
Actually, governor, can I get back to you tomorrow?
咱们明天必须见面
This meeting has to happen tomorrow.
我们没有时间了
Time is not on our side.
那我明天一早就给你打电话  谢谢
I'll get back to you first thing, then. Thank you.
你跟谁说了吗
Did you talk to anyone?
没有  我照你说的做了
No, I did everything the way you said to do it.
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
我也不知道
I don't know.
杰米  如果有什么问题  我必须得知道
Jamie, if there's a problem I need to know about it--
没有问题
There's no problem.
现在谎言就是真相
The lie is the truth now.
谎言就是真相  永远的真相
The lie is the truth and it is the truth forever.
明白吗
Do you understand me?
你只能靠自己了
You're on your fucking own with this.
你自己编造真相吧
Make up your own truth.
靠
Shit!
兰迪
Randy?
操
Fuck!
你觉得怎么样
Well, what do you think?
我们几年前就该这么做了
We should have done this years ago.
我们可以在这里放小公牛放到12月
We can run stockers out here 'till December.
那是你的新员工吗
That your new hire?
是的
Yes sir.
她怎么上去的
How did she get up there?
靠  我也不知道
Shit, I haven't figured that one out yet.
她像甲虫一样爬了上去
She ran up it like a damn beetle.
开了眼了
Never seen anything like it.
科尔比  几点了
Colby, what time it is?
吉米  太阳在你正上方
You know, Jimmy, when the sun's directly above you,
你觉得现在几点了
what time do you think that is?
吉米  你要去哪里吗
Jimmy, you got somewhere you need to be?
不是  利文斯顿的资格赛3点开始
Oh, no, it's just the qualifier in Livingston starts at 3.
如果弄完了  我可以
So if we're done here, is it okay to...?
怎么了  我付你的钱不够吗
What's the matter, I don't pay you enough?
不是
No, sir.
不  我在存钱
No, I just been saving it up.
我终于有钱办职业卡了  所以
Finally got enough to get my pro card, so...
今晚是我的第一场排位赛
Tonight's the first rodeo that counts toward my standings.
这种谋生方式太难了  吉米
It's a rough way to make a living, Jimmy.
要是骑烈马摔断胳膊  就很难
You break an arm chasing buckles, it's hard to...
很难继续打工了
it's hard to stay on any man's payroll.
明白
Yes, sir.
麻烦来了
Here goes the day.
州长要见我们
Governor wants to see us.
你是说州长想见你吧
You mean the Governor wants to see you.
我正在享受退休生活
I'm retired. And enjoying it.
她说的是我们俩
She said both of us.
我可以让直升机过来
I can bring the chopper out here.
一小时就能到海伦纳
We can be in Helena in an hour.
听起来很严重
Sounds important.
的确
Sounds like it.
如果真有那么严重  她应该来见我
If it's that important, she shouldn't mind coming to see me.
我在利文斯顿的牛仔竞技赛等她
And I'll be at the rodeo in Livingston.
我们可以回来
Well, we can get back by--
我说了我在牛仔竞技赛等她
I said I'll be at the rodeo.
我相信她的选民会很高兴看到她
I'm sure her voters would enjoy watching her
参与他们真正在乎的事情
partake in something they actually care about.
里普  决定一下今晚谁看牛群
Rip, decide who's stayin' with the herd tonight.
我就穿这身进城  我们
I'm gonna take this outfit to town and we're, uh...
我们去看吉米竞技表演
we'll go watch Jimmy rodeo.
好的  泰特
Okay. Hey, Teeter.
你今晚看牛群
You're with the herd tonight.
科尔比  你陪着她
Colby, you stay with her, too.
我怎么能阻碍你和自然的亲密接触呢  科尔比
Who am I to come between you and nature, Colby?
快问快答  谁在上面
Hey, real, quick, who's on top?
应该很明显吧
I don't think there's any debate about that.
我们去收拾一下进城
We're gonna go get cleaned up, go into town.
祝你晚上过得愉快  伙计
You have a great night, buddy.
不要做我不会做的事
Don't do anything I wouldn't do.
我希望你们俩
You know, I want both of you to just drop dead
立刻在我面前死去
right in front of me right now.
这是我的梦想
That would be a dream.
你很快就会有一个新梦想了
Oh, I think you're gonna have a new dream in a little while.
玩得开心
All right, you all have fun.
照顾好我们的朋友  好吗
And take care of our friend, okay?
慢慢来  他是个浪漫主义者
And go slow, he's a romantic.
你看起来像只拔了毛的鸡
Hey, hey, you look like a plucked mother fuckin' chicken.
谢谢  别掉下来了
Thank you. Don't fall.
好吗  上面真的很高
Okay? You're really high up.
她的嘴真不饶人啊
That one's got a real mouth on her.
我喜欢她
Yeah, I like that girl.
大家是不是都觉得我是山谷里最蠢的人
I guess everyone thinks I'm the dumbest man in the valley.
你可以握着她的手  里普
You can hold her damn hand, Rip.
谢谢爸爸
Thank you, Daddy.
我的牧场还能有我不知道的事么
As if something could happen on my ranch I don't know about.
真是的
Jesus Christ.
无名小孩
Kid drew No Name.
靠  那匹烈马太牛逼了
Oh, shit. That's a nasty bronc there.
去年那家伙在全国牛仔竞技赛出场了十个回合
That son of a bitch last year bucked ten rounds at the NFR
所有人都被甩下来了
and he threw every one of them in the dirt.
一匹价值十万的烈马啊
A hundred thousand dollar bucking horse, right there, probably, huh?
让他一定要专注
Better get his head in the game.
靠  吉米
Oh shit. Jimmy?
你什么都不说吗
Ain't gonna say nuthin'?
-嗯  我本来没想着过来的  -嗯
- Yeah, I didn't really plan this out past walking up here. - Yeah.
我在三叉市见过你
I saw you in Three Forks.
得了89分  赢了我兄弟
Scored an 89. Beat my brother.
我没见过你  不然我肯定会记得
Yeah, I didn't see you or I woulda remembered.
我当时在看台上
I was in the stands.
你是吉米·哈德森
You are Jimmy Hurdstram.
你
You, uh...
你知道我的名字
You know my name?
我说啦  我在三叉市见过你
Like I said. I saw you in Three Forks.
我叫米娅
I'm Mia.
咱俩好客套
Very professional of us.
我很想说点什么
I'm trying real hard to think of something to say.
但我真的不知道说什么
And just nothing's coming out.
你可以约我啊
You could ask me on a date.
嗯  是的
I could. I could do that.
那就约啊
So, do it.
我可以和你约会吗
Wanna go on a date?
嗯  好啊
Yes. Yeah.
靠  有点简单啊
Shit, that's kind of easy.
本来就不难呀
Ain't supposed to be hard.
通常都很难吧  我也不知道
It's usually pretty hard. I don't know.
吉米
Jimmy.
-那是你爸吗  -算是吧
- That your dad? - Kind of, yeah.
-你第几个出场  -第三
- What's your draw? - Third.
我会为你欢呼的
I'll be cheering for you.
我不会让你失望的
I'll give you something to cheer for.
祝你好运
Good luck.
蠢货
Hey, Dipshit.
请原谅  女士  我们还要赢牛仔竞技赛呢
Pardon us, ma'am. We've got a rodeo to win.
希望如此
Yeah, I hope so.
我居然吻了你
Can't believe I kissed you.
我不是那么主动的人
I'm not that forward.
我很喜欢  所以
I liked it, so...
吉米  天啊
Jimmy, Jesus.
你有没有经历过一个女孩看着你  你整个世界就停止了
Ever had a girl look at you and your whole world just stops?
每周六晚上都有
Every Saturday night.
好了  专注点
Now, come on, focus.
进去
Get your ass in there.
-你们看到她了吗  -我们看到了
- Did you see her? - Yes, we saw her.
看来今晚有位特别访客
Looks like we have a special visitor tonight.
蒙大拿州长佩里
Montana's very own Governor Perry.
你还真是不让人省心啊
You don't make it easy, do you?
我可不是这样的人  莉奈儿
Well, never my goal, Lynelle.
喝啤酒吗
You, uh, want a beer?
好啊  喝吧
Sure. Let's have a beer.
饿了吗
Hey, buddy, you hungry?
我给你买个玉米热狗
Let's go get you a corn dog.
我们去吃点东西
We're going to go get something to eat.
那么
So, um...
-州长  -杰米
- Governor. - Jamie.
我们能不能好好享受今晚
Can we just enjoy the evening
明天再谈这个问题
and talk about the problem tomorrow?
莉奈儿  这就是问题的好处
Come on, Lynelle, that's the one good thing about problems:
明天问题依然存在
they'll still be problems tomorrow.
你能给我讲讲你淫笑背后的计划吗
You want to walk me through the plan behind that dirty grin?
那要看情况了
Well, that all depends.
什么情况
On what?
你的安保人员有多少
On how big your security detail is.
-你被迫退休的生活如何  -极乐
- How's, uh... forced retirement? - Bliss.
-我跟你做个交易  -好
- I'll make you a deal. - All right.
我今晚给你答案  明天给你问题
I'll give you the solution tonight and the problem tomorrow.
你接受这个答案
You agree to the solution,
我们就可以装一整晚的青少年
and we can play teenager for the remainder of the night.
好吧  答案是什么
All right. What's the solution?
我任命杰米为临时检察长
I appoint Jamie interim Attorney General
杰米任命一个人
and Jamie appoints a person of your choosing
管理牲畜委员会
to run the Livestock Commission.
出事了
Something happened.
我的提议对本州最有利吗
Is what I'm proposing best for the state?
我也不知道
I don't know.
对你最有利吗  是的
Is it best for you? Yes.
对山谷的人最有利吗
Is it best for the people in this valley?
应该是的
I... I think so.
我心里真的这么想
In my heart, I think it is.
我们这么做的目的是什么
And we do all this with what goal in mind?
协商一个可以接受的投降
To negotiate an acceptable surrender.
我们要放弃什么
What are we surrendering?
你想去河里裸泳吗
You wanna go skinny dipping down in the river?
不想
No.
想要背部按摩吗
Wanna backrub?
不用了  谢谢
I don't. Thanks.
那你能帮我背部按摩吗
You wanna give me'un?
不能
No, I don't.
靠  你不喜欢女孩  对吧
Shit, you don't like girls, do ya?
我猜你肯定想暴操我海报上的男孩吧
Bet you want to pile drive one of them boys in my posters, don't ya?
不  我不想暴操你海报上的男孩
No, I don't want to pile drive one of the boys in your poster.
扯淡
Bullshit.
别这样  好吗
Can you not?
没事的  宝贝
It's all right, baby.
下一个到吉米了
Jimmy's next.
问题有很多
The problem-- there's plenty--
但最大的问题是
but problem number one is:
我找不到人替代杰米
I don't have anyone to replace Jamie.
那位战争英雄呢
What about the war hero?
问过了  他不愿意
Already asked him. He won't do it.
你这辈子从没询问过任何人
You've never asked anybody for anything in your life.
你只会下命令
You tell.
我可以去问他
I'll ask him.
他不会拒绝的
And he won't say no.
前提是你愿意
If that's what you want for him.
这是我一直以来对他的期望
It's all I've ever wanted for him.
那就让我在药片上加点糖
Then let me put a little sugar on this pill.
约翰·达顿承认他不是全能的了
John Dutton admitting that he can't do everything.
我可没有承认
I admitted no such thing.
孩子  加油  吉米
Okay, come on, kid. Come on, Jimmy.
醒醒  吉米
Wake the fuck up, Jimmy.
-准备好了  -最好是这样  抓紧缰绳
- Ready, ready, ready. - Better be. Get your bind.
加油  吉米
Let's go, Jimmy.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!